Finding Aid for Mike Wallace papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Television and newspaper career 1956-1963
  - WNTA Mike Wallace Interview February 1959-March 1961
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
      (includes press releases, syndication list, and administrative papers)
    - Chronological Broadcast Lists (Box 9)
    - Memos and Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Press Clippings (Box 9)
    - Syndication Files
      (includes booking schedules, information on promotional appearances, and correspondence)
      - Armed Forces Radio (Box 9)
      - Cleveland (WTTV) (Box 9)
      - Evansville, Indiana (WEHT) (Box 9)
      - Indianapolis (WTTY) (Box 9)
      - Kansas City (WDAF) (Box 9)
      - Los Angeles (KTLA) (Box 9)
      - Minneapolis (KMSP) (Box 9)
      - New York (WNTA) (Box 9)
      - Norfolk, Virginia (WTAR) (Box 9)
      - Oklahoma City (WKY) (Box 9)
      - Providence (WPRO) (Box 9)
      - Richmond, Virginia (WRVA) (Box 9)
      - St. Louis (KPLR) (Box 9)
      - Springfield, Massachusetts (WWLP) (Box 9)
      - Seattle (KTNT) (Box 9)
      - Tampa (WTVT) (Box 9)
    - Interviews
      - Behan, Brendan (Box 9)
      - Belafonte, Harry (Box 9)
      - Burrows, Abe October 16, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Cahn, Sammy March 2, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Damone, Vic September 27, 1960 (Box 9)
      - de Seversky, Major Alexander April 6, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Edmondson, Governor J. Howard November 19, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Havoc, June March 9, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Ionesco, Eugene December 6, 1960 (Box 9)
      - James, Harry, unused February, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Johnston, Eric, unused (Box 9)
      - Kramer, Stanley (Box 9)
      - Page, Geraldine October 22, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Quinn, Anthony October 25, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Robinson, Sugar Ray, unused (Box 9)
      - Roth, Dr. Russell January 27, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Saxon, John September 2, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Shulman, Charles October 17, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Veeck, Bill January, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Wertham, Dr. Frederic May 12, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Wright, Frank Lloyd March 1, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Wright, Mrs. Frank Lloyd May 26, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous programs and program proposals
    - The Hate That Hate Produced, (WNTA) July 22, 1959
      - Administrative (Box 9)
        (contains press releases, program summary and correspondence)
      - Press Clippings (Box 9)
    - The Race for Space April 1960 (Box 9)
      (contains booklet summary of show and correspondence)
    - Biography 1960-1963 (Box 9)
      (contains correspondence and review)
    - P.M. East, (Westinghouse Broadcasting Network) 1961-1962
      - Correspondence (Box 9)
      - Press Clippings (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
        (contains promotional material and memoranda)
      - Interviews
        - Bolt, Robert March 13, 1962 (Box 9)
        - Davis, John March 22, 1962 (Box 9)
        - McLendon, Sarah March 7, 1962 (Box 9)
        - Models June 8, 1961 (Box 9)
        - Obscenity May 1961 (Box 9)
        - Porter, Katherine Anne April 20, 1962 (Box 9)
        - Tully, Andrew March 7, 1962 (Box 9)
        - McCafferty, Jeannie May 15, 1961 (Box 9)
    - The Challenge (Box 9)
      (contains outline for proposed series and script for pilot episode)
    - The Great Men (Box 9)
      (contains outline for new series and script for first episode)
    - The People's Parade (3 scripts) (Box 9)
    - New Program Ideas (Box 9)
      (contains outlines for several proposed series)
    - William Morris Agency 1960-1962 (Box 9)
      (contains documents relating to contract with agent)
    - Latin America Documentary 1962 (Box 9)
      (contains research material for proposed documentary)
    - Brooklyn, Psychiatric Society Panel Discussion November 16, 1962 (Box 9)
      (contains transcript of the program)
- Photographs
  The Photographs in this collection are broken down into four folders: Formal Portraits, Informal Portraits, Mike Wallace with guests, and Ben Hecht with guests.
  - Formal portraits (Box 9)
  - Informal portraits (Box 9)
  - Mike Wallace with guests (Box 9)
  - Ben Hecht with guests (Box 9)